MATTHEW DIAZ

Rockledge, Florida 32955 954-994-5441 diazmatt2004@gmail.com

First-year computer science student, future Web Developer, with 2 years of Web Development experience, and coding experience. Before entering school, I would find different ways to practice, learn, and implement code into projects. My passion for web development lead me to Eastern Florida where I am working on my Associates Degree, then into University of Central Florida to get my bachelor's degree in computer science.

Currently, I am taking a course on Zero To Mastery Academy called "Complete Web Developer in 2023: Zero to Mastery". In this course I have learned to strengthen my skills in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, SCSS, DOM, JavaScript, React, Node, and many more languages/concepts.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coordinator

1/2020 to Present

Discount Tire

Rockledge, Florida

- Enhanced performance through collaboration with diverse teams.
- Planned and managed operations to achieve objectives within budgets.
- Organized teams and resources to optimize timely deliverables.
- · Coordinated with other supervisors, combining group efforts to achieve goals.
- Provided leadership, insight and mentoring to newly hired employees to supply knowledge of various company programs.
- Trained employees on best practices and protocols while managing teams to maintain optimal productivity.
- · Delegated work to staff, setting priorities and goals.
- · Resolved customer complaints or answered customers' questions.

Web Developer

10/2022 to Present

Zero To Mastery

Remote

- Designed websites, portals and large-scale web applications for multiple clients.
- Implemented improvements to boost site performance.
- Troubleshot, tested and remedied issues before software deployment.
- Maintained strong education in latest technologies, software and hardware products for use in various projects.
- Built layouts according to customer parameters using HTML5 and CSS3.
- Learned coding languages such as; HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, SCSS, DOM, JavaScript, React, Node, and more.

SKILLS

Scripting Languages: Python, Javascript

JavaScript Libraries and Frameworks

Responsive Web Design

Time Management and Prioritization

Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, and more

Version Control Systems: Git, Github

Back-End and Database Skills

EDUCATION

Rockledge High School

High school or equivalent Rockledge, Florida 8/2019 to 5/2023

Eastern Florida State College

Associate Melbourne, Florida 9/2023 to 9/2024